New York State Public Employees Federation, AFL-CIO, Environmental Conservation Division (PEF/ENCON); Records apap114
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Memorabilia, 1984-1985; 1988; 1999; Undated; 8; 0.2 cubic ft.
  - Service Employees International Union, Sweeney/Cordtz Campaign, Cloth Promotional Sign, 1988 (Box 1 (8-Memorabilia), Folder 9)
  - Build Strength for a Better Future, Poster, Undated (Box 1 (8-Memorabilia), Folder 10)
  - My Broken Arm Cost More than Hers to Fix, Poster, Undated (Box 1 (8-Memorabilia), Folder 11)
  - Vote Richard Croak Rensselaer County Legislator, Poster, Undated (Box 1 (8-Memorabilia), Folder 12)
  - New York's Proposed Health Plan For Members Is Stranger Than a $3 Bill, Poster, Undated (Flat-file 1)